(Sheldon:)...I happened to gaze out the window
and a brassiere caught my eye.
(Sheldon:)Do those look familiar?
(Penny:)How the hell did you get them up
on that telephone wire?
(Sheldon:)When you understand the laws of physics,
Penny, anything is possible.
And may I add:
Mua-ha-ha.
- Get them down.
- Apologize.
(Raj:)- Never.
- Then I suggest...
(Sheldon:)...you get a very long stick
and play panty piñata.
(Penny:)Look, wait, Sheldon.
(Penny:)This has gotten out of hand. Okay.
(Penny:)I've done some stupid things,
you've done some stupid things.
How about call it even,
move on with our lives?
(Sheldon:)I've done no stupid things.
- Look, you've gotta meet me halfway here.
- I am.
(Sheldon:)I'm willing to concede that you've
done some stupid things.
(Leonard:)Hey, you guys are talking again. Good.
(Leonard:)What happened?
(Scene:)Leonard,
remember when I said it was on?
(Penny:)Well, now it's junior rodeo on.